Hello, this is Week 32 release notes, let's get started now
Yeah, I'll start with the new features. We were originally only able to add YouTube videos.
Now that we've added support for uploading video and audio files, we're able to offer trough summaries for a wide variety of content.
So, for example, if we're having a meeting offline, or if we're listening to a lecture, and we record it, or if we have a recording of it
we can create a Traw summarization based on that and even if we don't have subtitles, Traw will automatically create them for us.
So you can easily create summaries by just uploading a file, and it's a feature that a lot of people have been asking for.
We've released a Zapier integration so you can automate your summaries on the Traw.
So what you can do with this automation is you can share a trough summer with multiple services.
So, for example, you could send those transcribed summaries from a YouTube video to a notion, or you could organize them into a spreadsheet.
and a whole bunch of other services, making it much easier for people to utilize Traw in their own workflows.
And then lastly, the iOS application, because a lot of people use YouTube on mobile, how can we make it easier to watch YouTube videos
and we've been working on that, and if you download the Traw AI application, which is now available on the app store
and you can now add a YouTube video from your mobile, or you can upload a file that you've taken or recorded on your phone and turn it into a summer.
And in the YouTube application, if you're watching a video and you hit share, and you select the Tumblr app, it will automatically add the video summer to the
you can create
Yeah, and then there's a bunch of minor changes, because our Traw is still in its early stages, so it doesn't have a lot of bells and whistles.
There were some things that weren't working.
We've now switched the video between collections so that it can now be moved between them.
And then there was an issue where sometimes foreign language videos would now come up in English when you summarize them.
We've added an update to recognize and translate languages a little more accurately.
We've also made a number of changes to the quality of our summaries to ensure that users always get the same quality results.
We've also made improvements to the quality of the documentation. And the original service menu names were originally only available in English.
The service has now started to support a wider range of languages in the UI for six different countries.
That's all for now, and I'd like to give you a quick overview of our upcoming updates.
Traw has been provided for free until now, but since we are using a lot of AI features, we are inevitably going to charge for it.
That's coming soon, and we'll let you know, and if you sign up before it's paid, you'll get some special perks.
So stay tuned, and we'll be releasing an Android app just like we did for iOS.
Right now, the Zapier integration is focused on utilizing Traw summary, but in the future, we'll be able to do things like automatically add videos from YouTube.
will be added, and we're also working on some design updates to the UI across the service.
And there's a lot more in the works. That concludes our release notes. Thank you.